(upbeat music)
- Zustand is a small, a fast,
and a scalable state management solution
with a simplified data flow
between the store and the components.
Previously, we saw how to create a store,
how to create functions,
how to access and update the store data,
and also access multiple states to update the components.
Now it's your turn to make the best of Zustand
with a new challenge.
So we have this to-do list, we can add items to it.
New item.
We can cross items off the list,
and then clear the ones that are completed.
We can decide to display only the active elements,
or the completed ones, or display them all.
So this exercise is to learn how to synchronize the state
across multiple components of your app.
So let's go check out the startup project.
You see that we have multiple state variables.
So we use the React API,
and here the goal is to refactor the app.
Refactor the app by using Zustand only.
So the application should contain a single
and a centralized store.
You see that we have multiple components
in order to compose the UI.
So we have the header, and the footer.
And also to apply the powerful concept of React,
which is composition,
we divide the user interface into multiple units,
multiple components.
And so the goal will be to allow every component
to subscribe to the state change by calling,
by calling the hook store.
So the first task will be
for you to create a store to centralize the data
as a single source of truth.
And then the second task will be
to update all the components
with the same single source of truth,
so to call the hook in order to access, read the states,
and then update the state directly from the components.
So good luck to you,
and up next we see the solutions together to this challenge.